

ABOUT ME

Hello there I am Abhinash Bhagat and currently lives in Bharatpur, Nepal. I am working as the Joomla developer in Greenline Media Pvt. Ltd. And I also am experienced in the data analysis field, acquied while working as the Data Analyst.

SKILL

Joomla

Data Analysis

Web Scrapping

Task Automation

LANGUANGE







ABHINASH **BHAGAT**

DATA ANALYST

CONTACT

- +977 9843128852
- O Chitwan, Nepal
- www.abhinashbhagat.com.np

EXPERIENCE

2018-2022 JOOMLA DEVELOPER

Greenline Media Pvt .Ltd.

I have worked as the Joomla Developer in Greenline Media Pvt. Ltd. for almost 4 years now. And with the running time, I learned quite an experience here.

2014-2017 DATA ANALYST

Upwork

I have been doing the data analysis as a freelancing in upwork. And to be honest, I am enjoying this change in field from websites to Data.

2012-2014

WEB SCRAPPER

Upwork

I have been doing the web scrapping as a freelancing in upwork. I earned pretty good experience doing this by providing my clients what they exactly needed.

EDUCATION

2005-2020 - Secondary Education

Pokhara University

2021-Till Date - Bachelors in IT

Tribhuwan University